

PROFILE

Experienced Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Software Product Lifecycle, Business Planning, pertains Management, Immersive Technology solutions, like Augmented Reality & Virtual Reality and Connected Digital Enterprise solutions. Strong consulting professional and Business Manager with 19+ years of Industry experience

CONTACT

PHONE: 944-446-7273

LinkedIn Profile https://www.linkedin.com/in/chandra kant-aknurwar-4556bb12/

EMAIL:

c.aknurwar@gmail.com
c_aknurwar@yahoo.com

HOBBIES

Mobility Application Exploration Travelling Building people Network

Chandrakant Aknurwar

Industry Advisor, IoT Solutions- Immersive Technology, Engineering & Industrial Services at Tata Consultancy Services

EDUCATION

THE OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY

2022

Growth & Transformational Leadership Program (G&T Phoenix)

Nagpur University

2002

Masters in computer applications

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tata Consultancy Services [XR Consultant] 2013- Present

[Describe your responsibilities and achievements in terms of impact and results. Use examples but keep in short.]

Sasken technologies [Lead Engineer] 2010–2013

Sepura ODC set up and managed a team of 35 members to successfully deliver Sepura ruggedized device software product in the areas of embedded applications.

Welldoc [Lead Engineer] 2009 to 2010

Building Mobile solution which helps to provide a holistic, evidence-based approach for pre-diabetes, diabetes, hypertension, heart failure and behavioral health.

Kyocera Wireless Sr. Engineer 2006–2009

Lead a team of 9 engineers in the development of widget-based UI framework on BREW eco system.

Satyam Computer Services Software Engineer 2004 - 2006

Feature enhancements for CDMA Mobile phones. Development of BREW application layer for BENQ and integration with feature phones. Piloting and development of NextGen UI on the mobile device side

SKILLS

